<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<ghosts>
    <ghost>
        <name>Elizabeth Williams</name>
        <type>Samca</type>
        <background>An evil spirit, said to curse children and pregnant women with illness.</background>
        <evidence>Remanence of Moldy Cheese</evidence>
        <evidence>Oozing Slime</evidence>
        <backstory>Samca - Romanian Folklore
            Ms. Williams was always jealous that her colleagues were having children, but she couldn't.
            Of course this wasn't a fault of her own. Her medical history prevented her from getting pregnant.
            Its was a normal amount of jealousy at first. In order to cope with her emotions she always offered to
            watch her friend's kids. Becoming what she called herself, their "second mom." One day her current
            partner left her because of her inability to have children. It shifted to all downhill from there. She
            became deranged, keeping her friends kid's, saying she's their mother, not anyone else. Police showed up
            to her house because she was keeping the kids hostage. They had no choice but to use lethal force on her.
            Ms. Williams to this day exhibits jealousy and is still on the mindset of having her own children. When
            you are around her DO NOT bring your children or pregnant wife anywhere near her. No good will come out of it.</backstory>
    </ghost>
    <ghost>
        <name>Jackson Smith</name>
        <type>Poltergeist</type>
        <background>
            A clown doll, likes to mess with the mind of intruders on it's property.
            Will laugh behind you randomly and when you turn around, it will vanish once eye contact is made</background>
        <evidence>Ghost messed with your mind causing hallucinations</evidence>
        <evidence>Room has a slight scent of sulfur</evidence>
        <backstory>TODO BRUDDAH</backstory>
    </ghost>
    <ghost>
        <name>Edgar Miller</name>
        <type>Demon</type>
        <background>
            A supernatural being, typically associated with evil.
            Is summoned to do works of malice, or to create chaos amongst those it haunts.</background>
        <evidence>The ghost has entered the physical realm and harmed your body causing lacerations</evidence>
        <evidence>A flash of a figure pops up in the corner. Likely to be hallucinations.</evidence>
        <backstory>Demon - Multiple Folklore
            When Edgar was just a little boy he would work very hard for his allowance.
            When he saved up enough money he would go down to the local hardware store. Amongst the items he bought,
            they were items always used for torture devices. First victim he used them on was his Skipper, his dog.
            It was just a little nick at first, then slowly it progressed. As he got older his victims started to vary.
            The point of no return was when he used his very first tool, a power drill, on a random stranger at the local park.
            Law Enforcement took him in, Edgar was facing charges projecting life in prison. Upon awaiting trial he found a
            way to quickly grab his escorting officer's weapon. Taking four people out before taking his own life.
            The motives of Edgar's behavior are unknown. All we know is his sadism is very much apparent on the victims
            he haunts today.</backstory>
    </ghost>
    <minighosts>
        <minighost>
            <name>Angry Grandma</name>
            <type>Apparition</type>
        </minighost>
        <minighost>
            <name>Cranky Boss</name>
            <type>Haunt</type>
        </minighost>
        <minighost>
            <name>Sultry Maiden</name>
            <type>Shade</type>
        </minighost>
        <minighost>
            <name>Saucy Ferret</name>
            <type>Specter</type>
        </minighost>
    </minighosts>
</ghosts>
